我们 是水晶
♪ We ♪ are the crystal
战士
♪ gems
我们总能拯救世界
♪ we'll always save the day
如果你认为我们不行
♪ and if you think we can't, ♪
我们总能找到方法
♪ we'll always find a way
这就是为什么这个世界
♪ that's why the people
的人
♪ of this world
相信
♪ believe in
石榴
♪ Garnet
紫晶
♪ Amethyst
和珍珠
♪ and Pearl
和史蒂文!
and Steven!
对剑宣誓
欢迎关注微博@UUU字幕组，获取最新熟肉信息！
出品
UUU字幕组
翻译
presisco
校对
特效
presisco
压制
明日高照 衣衫洁净
♪ The sun is bright, our shirts are clean ♪
我们坐在大洋之上
♪ we're sitting up above the sea ♪
快来分享果酱小曲
♪ come on and share this jam with me ♪
桃或李或是草莓
♪ peach or plum or strawberry ♪
任何水果都可以
♪ any kind is fine, you see ♪
快来分享果酱小曲
♪ come on and share this jam with me ♪
我会尽力
♪ I'll do my best
为果酱添加应有的甜蜜
♪ to give this jam the sweetness it deserves ♪
而我则保鲜
♪ and I'll keep it fresh
我伴着美味蜜饯而歌
♪ I'm jammin'on these tasty preserves ♪
相互搭配 各种原料
♪ ingredients in harmony
我们一起完美混合
♪ we mix together perfectly
快来分享果酱小曲
♪ come on and share this jam with me ♪
果酱伙伴!
Jam buds!
表演的不错
Nice jam session.
别忘的最好的部分
Don't forget the best part.
逃向你们的主人吧!
Run back to your masters!
告诉他们 我们无所畏惧!
Tell them we're not afraid of your kind!
谢谢你拯救了我的果酱小食
Thanks for saving my jam snack.
不幸的是 它还是会因我遭殃
Unfortunately, it's not safe from me.
你真是个优秀的剑士啊 康妮
You're such a good sword fighter, Connie.
真的? 我刚才只是在随便挥舞这个而已
Really? I was just swinging this thing around.
我并不清楚自己在做什么
I don't really know what I'm doing.
但我非常想学习如何使用真剑
But I'd love to learn how to use a real sword.
哦! 史蒂文有个主意!
Oh! Steven has an idea!
你想让我做什么?
You want me to do what?
你一定要教康妮剑术
You should train Connie to sword fight.
她现在已经非常出色了
She's already so good.
史蒂文!
Steven!
没错 你帮我打败了飞行机器人
But you are. Y-you helped me fight the robot floaty thing,
她打败了自己的邪恶克隆体
she took down that evil clone of herself,
呃...还有刚才的那些坏海鸥
uh...Those mean seagulls just now.
你现在接触这种东西还是太小了
You're awfully young to begin something like this.
但我想我开始与玫瑰·石英一起战斗时
But I suppose I was only a few thousand years old
也才几千岁而已
when I begin fighting alongside Rose Quartz.
怎么 康妮?
Yes, Connie?
求求你 我想学
Please, I want to learn.
我是指 我不知道以后会发生什么
I mean, I don't know what will happen in the future.
但如果出现了危险的情况
But if something dangerous comes along,
我不想成为负担 我想要帮忙!
I don't want to be a burden. I want to help!
我想帮助史蒂文 与他肩并肩战斗!
I want to be there for Steven, to fight by his side!
地球也是我的家 我就不能帮忙保护吗?
The earth is my home, too. Can't I help protect it?
好吧
O-okay.
如果你是这么认为的 那我们该开始了
If that's how you feel, we should get started.
等等 现在?
Wait, now?
你还好吗?
You okay?
这可能要花些功夫适应
It can take some getting used to.
嘿 你们两个 这里
Hey, you two. This way.
比比看
Race you.
这是个远古天空角斗场 康妮
This is an ancient sky arena, Connie,
地球独立战争早期的部分战役也是在这里发生的
where some of the first battles for earth took place.
我就是在这里了解了
It was here that I became familiar with
人类对于骑士的概念
the human concept of being a knight,
完全献身于某个人或理念
completely dedicated to a person and a cause.
你必须要成为这样的人 康妮--
This is what you must become, Connie--
勇敢 无私 忠诚--骑士
brave, selfless, loyal--a knight.
我们先从躬身开始 首先对我 你的老师
We begin with a bow. First to me, your teacher.
然后是你的君主
And now again to your liege.
好的 我的君主
Okay. My liege.
骑士小姐
Miss knight.
我希望你们两个能严肃点
I hope you two are taking this seriously.
好的 夫人
Yes, ma'am.
酷 全息珍珠
Cool. Hologram Pearl.
首先 这个全息珍珠是你的对手
To begin, this holo-Pearl will be your opponent.
第0级 初学者设置
Level 0, beginner set.
你是否愿意进入战斗?
Do you wish to engage in combat?
当然!
Yes!
史蒂文?
Steven?
哦! 呃 我很抱歉
Oh! Um, I'm sorry.
抱歉 抱歉 抱歉 抱歉
Sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry.
条件反射
Reflex.
呃 你小心点 我会去那里待着
Uh, you just be careful, and I will go over here.
好吧 一切先从你的站姿开始
All right. Everything begins with your stance.
要记住...你为他而战
Remember...♪ you do it for him
而你愿再次出征
♪ and you would do it again ♪
你为她而战
♪ you do it for her
也就是说 你为他而战
♪ that is to say you'll do it for him ♪
双腿 迈开
♪ keep your stance wide
保持低的重心
♪ keep your body lowered
当你移动向前
♪ as you're moving forward
平衡是关键
♪ balance is the key
右脚 左脚
♪ right foot, left foot
现在加快速度
♪ now go even faster
而当你向后移动
♪ and as you're moving backwards ♪
一定看向我
♪ keep your eyes on me
双腿 迈开
♪ keep my stance wide.
好
good.
保持低的重心
♪ Keep my body lowered.
对
right
当我移动向前
♪ As I'm moving forward
集中注意
concentrate.
你不想让他活命吗?
Don't you want him to live?
右脚 左脚
♪ Right foot, left foot
对 但全身协调一致
yes, but put your whole body into it.
拥有的一切 拥有的自我
♪ Everything you have, everything you are ♪
你要付出 在那战场上
♪ you've got to give on the battlefield ♪
当一切变得混乱
♪ when everything is chaos ♪
而你只有你的内心
♪ and you have nothing but the way you feel ♪
你的头脑还有剑
♪ your strategy and a sword ♪
你只想到了心目中的
♪ you just think about the life you'll have ♪
战后一起的生活
♪ together after the war
你就会为她而战
♪ and then you do it for her ♪
你才相信你你能赢
♪ that's how you know you can win ♪
你为她而战
♪ you do it for her
也就是说 你为他而战
♪ that is to say you'll do it for him ♪
你已 明了
♪ deep down you know
你非生为战斗
♪ you weren't built for fighting ♪
但这不能阻止你为此付出
♪ but that doesn't mean you're not prepared to try ♪
别人 不知
♪ what they don't know
你真正的优势
♪ is your real advantage
当你为某人活你无惧赴死
♪ when you live for someone you're prepared to die ♪
其实 我懂 我只是个人类
♪ deep down, I know that I'm just a human ♪
没错
True.
但我知道我能
♪ But I know that I can
但你知道你能
♪ but you know that you can
拔剑去战斗
♪ draw my sword and fight
♪ draw your sword and fight
我的生命虽短
♪ with my short existence.
对
good
但可以很非凡
♪ I can make a difference.
没错 非常棒!
Yes, excellent!
我能在他左右
♪ I can be there for him
我能做骑士
♪ I can be his knight
我能为他而战
♪ I can do it for him
你为她而战
♪ you do it for her
现在你再做一次
♪ okay, now, do that again
好的 夫人
yes, ma'am.
你为她而战 而你会说
♪ You do it for her, and now you say ♪
我为他而战
♪ I'll do it for him
如何与他人交谈
康妮!
Connie!
史蒂文手中的书源自卡耐基的名书 "人性的弱点"( How to Win Friends and Influence People)
嘿 史蒂文
Hey, Steven.
康妮 等等
Connie, wait.
啊 真准时
Ah, right on time.
我们能先谈一下吗?
Can we talk for a moment?
当然 怎么了?
Sure. What's up?
我们还有重要的训练要完成 康妮
We have important training to do, Connie.
好的 女士
Yes, ma'am.
她最近进步非常大 史蒂文
She's been making great strides, Steven.
她会成为你的得力部下
She's going to be an asset to you.
喔 石榴
Wow, Garnet.
那真是我听过的最有趣的故事
That was the funniest thing I've ever heard.
石榴 喜剧之王
Garnet, master of comedy.
呦 史蒂文
Yo, Steven.
你怎么一脸苦逼的站在那?!
Why are you standing there all sad like that?!
呃 康妮正跟着珍珠学习剑术
W-well, Connie is taking sword-fighting lessons from Pearl.
但我觉得训练有点太过了
But I think it's getting a little too serious.
她想让康妮替我完成所有危险的事
She wants Connie to do all this dangerous stuff for me.
这很正常
That makes sense.
你什么意思?
What do you mean?
很久前的战争中 珍珠非常自豪
Back during the war, Pearl took pride
能为你的母亲拿生命冒险
in risking her destruction for your mother.
她将玫瑰看得比什么都重要--
She put Rose Quartz over everything--
高过理智 无视后果 不惧死亡
over logic, over consequence, over her own life.
你还好吗 伙计?
You okay, dude?
我得做点什么!
I have to do something!
谢谢你告诉我这些! 再见!
Thanks for telling me that! Bye!
记着 康妮
Remember, Connie.
在激烈战斗中 史蒂文才是最重要的
In the heat of battle, Steven is what matters.
而你无足轻重
You don't matter.
我无足轻重
I don't matter.
现在 我们开始吧!
Now, let us begin!
康妮?
Connie?
康妮 你在哪?
Connie, where are you?
康妮!
Connie!
你不会刚好看到了康妮 是吧?
You wouldn't have happened to see Connie, would you?
探测到未注册战斗人员
Unregistered combatant detected.
康妮!
Connie!
史蒂文? 你在这里干嘛?
Steven? What are you doing out here?
康妮 我不想让你在做这些了--不能独自一人
Connie, I don't want you to do this anymore--not alone.
不 史蒂文 我现在明白了
No, Steven. I understand now.
你的遗产 你的使命--你是一切!
Your legacy, your destiny--you are everything!
而我--我什么都不是
And I--I am nothing.
但我能为你做这个 我可以为你效劳
But I can do this for you. I can give you my service.
不! 我不需要！
No! I don't want you to.
史蒂文 我这是为了你啊!
Steven, I'm doing this for you!
我得能够保护你
I need to be able to protect you.
但如果由你来保护我
But if you're the one protecting me,
那又有谁保护你呢?
then who's the one protecting you?
迟早有一天 我们会遭遇非常强大的敌人
Someday soon, we may be fighting some really bad guys.
而当那一天来临时 我希望与你战斗 一起
And when that day comes, I want to fight with you, together.
所以 求求你 你愿意跟我一起分享果酱吗?
So, please, won't you share this jam with me?
这真是简单太多了
This is much easier.
这就是重点
That's the idea.
不论面对什么 我们共同面对!
No matter what comes, we do this together!
史蒂文!
Steven!
史蒂文 不要干涉 她需要独自面对我
Steven, don't interfere. She needs to take me on herself.
为什么? 我们是团队
Why? We're a team.
她是草莓...
She's the strawberry...
...而他是饼干
...And he's the biscuit!
而我们则是
And that makes us
果酱
jam
伙伴
buds
蛤?
Wha...?
够了!
Enough!
不!
No!
在实际战斗中 史蒂文可不会及时拯救你!
In a real battle, Steven won't be there to save you!
错 我会的!
Yes, I will!
史蒂文 你根本不了解
Steven, you don't know that.
错 我了解!
Yes, I do!
如果康妮要战斗 我们要一起战斗!
If Connie is going to fight, we're going to fight together!
没错!
That's right!
你不应接近任何战斗!
You shouldn't be anywhere near the fight!
你太过重要了!
You're too important!
并不是!
I am not!
当然 你就是!
Yes, you are!
不!
No!
你为什么不让我为你做这些呢 玫瑰! ?
Why won't you just let me do this for you, Rose!?
我...我是指...让她 做这些
I...I mean...Let her do this.
你为什么不让康妮为你做这些?
Why won't you let Connie do this for you?
今天就到此为止吧
That's enough for today.
嘿 珍珠...
Hey, Pearl...
我不是故意给你的训练捣乱的
I didn't mean to mess up your training.
但你那些 "你毫不重要"的言论真的令我害怕
But all that "you're nothing"talk was really freaking me out.
玫瑰让你感觉你毫不重要吗?
Did Rose make you feel like you were nothing?
玫瑰让我感觉我最为重要
Rose made me feel like I was everything.
我现在了解了你们相互间多么在意彼此
I see now how deeply you care about each other.
那会让你们都成为伟大的骑士!
That will make you both great knights!
康妮基本上是个专家了
Connie is practically an expert.
所以 史蒂文 你要花很多功夫赶上康妮
So, Steven, you have a lot of catching up to do.
哦 我真是太高兴了
Oh, I'm so excited.
我等不及进行空中与水下决斗训练了
I can't wait for the midair and underwater dueling exercises.
这会非常有趣的!
It's going to be boodles of fun!
康妮的装束与战斗风格源自印度喀啦啦的卡拉里帕亚特和龙珠Z
本集中多处战斗镜头源自少女革命
康妮用的是弯刀 而珍珠和全息珍珠用的是轻剑
如果我可以做到
♪ If I could begin to be
你对我期望的一半
♪ half of what you think of me
我愿意做任何事
♪ I could do about anything
我愿学会像你一样，去爱
♪ I could even learn how to love like you ♪